Maltese, Serphin R.; Papers apap382
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Constituent Case Files, 1990-2008; 3.6 cubic ft.
  - Peterssen, Irene, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Petrosino, Josephine, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Petsche, Fred, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Pfisterer, Anna, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Pfreundschuk, Walter, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Phelan, Daniel and Helene, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Pikul, Flora, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Pilitsch, Lydia, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Pipia, Jenny, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Pipitone, Gaspare, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Piseitelli, Rose, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Pitcock, Donna, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Pizzarusso, Frank, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Platt, William, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Plummer, Margaret, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Poliszczok, Annette and John, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Poliziano, Angelo, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Poltorak, James, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Ponsat, Antwon, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Pope, Andrew, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Pope, Paul David, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Posekel, Kathryn, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Postiglion, Gerard, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Potts, Raymond, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Poturalski, Celia, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Poundt, John, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Powers, Alfred, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Prasad, Shirley, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Princi, Salvatore, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Profera, Peter, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Psomiades, Dean and Claire, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Puglisi, Pat, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Quaglia, Bill, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Quagliata, Peter, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Quandt, Ida, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Quattrochi, Vincent L., 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Questore, Joseph, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Quinn, Carol, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Quinn, Ed, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Quinones, Naomi, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Rady, Marian, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Rahman, Ehsan, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Rahmani, Mirela, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Raines, Gloria, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Rainone, Benedetta, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Rallo, Mary, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Ramos, Martha, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Ramrup, Parsram, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Ramsey, Madeline, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Randazzo, Carmine, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Rapp, Bernard, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Rappl, Frank, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Rassmann, Margaret, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Rastelli, Margaret, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Rathour, Amric, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Rauh, Elizabeth, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Razack, Bibi, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Reich, Bernard, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Reiss, Richard, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Rescigno, Ferdinand, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Residents of 47-26 49th St. Woodside, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Ricatto, Michael, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Ricca, Gail, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Ricca, Josephine, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Ricci, Susan, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Richardson, Marianne, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Richtman, Herbert, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Rienecker, Roberta, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Riley, Laura D'Attile, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Riomayor, Josephine, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Riportilla, Peter, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Ritter, Auriel, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Rivas, Nashla, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Rivera, Camille, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Rivera, Ivette, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Rizzo, Charles, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Roach, Michael, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Roach, Mr., 2001 (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Roberts, Fred, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Rodrigo, Maria, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Rodriguez, Jean Ferrara, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Rodriguez, Margaret, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Rodriguez, Ray, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Rogen, Anne, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Roldan, Tori, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Rolison, Senator Jay, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Roman, Candida, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Romanelli, Mary Theresa, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Romono, Joseph, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Rondinella, Pete, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Ronisi, Carol, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Roopnarain, Jasodia, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Rosa, Chris, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Rosina, Margaret, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Ross, Rev. Michael, Undated (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Rossi, Mark, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Roth, Barbara, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Roth, Phyllis, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Rowan, Dianna, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Rudzewick, Ken, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Ruggiero, David, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Ruiz, Carol, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Rummel, Marie, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Rupert, Roland, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Russo, Carol Ann, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Ruzalski, Joe, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Ryland, Matilda, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Saffa, Patricia Amoruso, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Saffioti, Pauline, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Safuto, Ellen, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Sallizzi, Mary Ann, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Samaritan Foundation, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Samuels, Isaac, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - SanClementi, Anna, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Sander, Emma, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - Santangelo, Margaret, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Santaromita, Joseph, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Santiago, Dennis, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Santoro, Frances, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Santoro, Janet, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Santoro, John, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Saparata, Edward and Victoria, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Sarafino, Virginia, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Sassmann, Arthur, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Savaglio, Eugene, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Savella, Louis, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Savello, Sarah, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Sawicki, Joseph, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - Scala, Mamie, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Scavone, Celeste, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Schatz, Mary, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - Schayne, Christopher, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - Scherer, Hazel, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - Schimenti, Barbara, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - Schleger, Arthur, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - Schmidt, John, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Schneider, Henry, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Schneider, John, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Schoenmuller, William, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Schultz, Ann, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Schultz, Martin, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Schuster, Ann, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Scianno, Antoinette, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Scichilore, Riccardo, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Scigliano, Rose, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Scott, Jim, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Seewald, Michael, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Segarra, Angel, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Seiff, Jerome, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Seminerio, Assemblyman Tony, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Severin, Lee, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Sexton, James, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Shanahan, Claire, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Shanley, Regina, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Sharma, Bhim, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Sheahan, Michael, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sheehan, Bill, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Sheridan, Candice, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Shore, Phil, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Shulman, Claire, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Shusterich, Ed, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Simonaitis, Vita, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Simonetti, Susan, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Simonitsch, Rosemary, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Sinatra, Sal, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Sinatra, Sam, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Smith, Beverly, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Smith, Bruce, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Smith, Murray, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Sokolovic, Anne, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Solow, Bernard, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Sommer, Thelma, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Sommersberger, John and Helga, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Sorrentino, Luciano, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Sorvillo, Michael, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Southwick, Lynn, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Spahl, Ilse, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Sparaco, Diana, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Spiro, Joan, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Sproviero, Rose, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - St. Johns Lutheran School, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Stahl, Stella, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Stalzer, John, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Stamm, John, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Stapf, Ruth, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Steckiewicz, Andrzej, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Steffa, Anthony and Judith, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Stein, Elizabeth, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Stephen, Virginia, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Stetz, Margaret, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Stewart, Jerry, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Stoike, Richard, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Strauss, Janet, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Stroble, David, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Sukrajchari, Ramnauth, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Sumsky, Kathy, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Sweeney, Magdalene, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Sydorko, Michael, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Tafilaj, Gani, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Tarpey, Helen, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Taylor, Yvonne, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Tenistokle, Mary, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Theodore, Antonie, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Thompson, Barbara, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Tinghitella, Mary Grace, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Tivadar, Vasile, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Toro, Pastore, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Torres, Lorraine, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Toscano, Barbara, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Trimboli, Flora, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Trobiano, Joseph, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Tschinkel, Mary, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Tucci, John, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Turello, Marion, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Turner, Brenda, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Tychanski, Bogdan, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Uhl, Joanne, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Ulmer, Madeline, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Urso, Lucille, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Utano, Anthony, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Valenti, Nicolo, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Valentin, Dimas, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Valley, Anne, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Valverde, Frank, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Vargas, Elvin, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Vasco, Frances, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Vasquez, Angel, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Vasquez, Debra, Undated (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Vera, Guadalupe, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Vetere, Pat, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Viano, John, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Viera, Marilyn, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Vilcea, Jasmina, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Viola, Vito, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Vitkavase, Anthony, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Volino, Josephine, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Voll, Bertha, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Vrooman, Beatrice, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Vurgos, Federico, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Waffenschmidt, Bob, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Wagner, Elsa, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Wagner, Kathleen, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Wagner, Wilhelm, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ward, Robert, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Waxman, Henry (Metromining), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Weidner, Madeline, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Weigel, Alice, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Weingaertner, Josephine, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Weiss, Lori, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Werkmeister, Lucille, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Wertheimer, Margaret, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Westrick, Robert, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Whalley, Gene, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - White, William, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Wiehl, Virginia, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Wilkinson, Ellen, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Winsch, William, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Wissert, Barbara, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Wlaysewski, John, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Wolfe, Josefa, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Wolff, Margaretha, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Worko, Joanne, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Wuerth, Marta, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Yoskowitz, Anita, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Zackaria, Joanne, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Zanzonico, Nicholas, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Zecca, Carla, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Zummo, Michael, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Zuzzi, Pat, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Post-Senate Files, 2009-2021; 1.0 cubic ft.
  This series chronicles Serphin Maltese's activities after he left the New York State Senate in 2009. This includes his work with the Triangle Fire Memorial Association, Italian American membership organizations, the New York State Conservative Party, veterans, Christ the King High School, and Queens area organizations. The types of records in this series include correspondence, newsletters, flyers, clippings, and informational documents.
  - Bloomberg Designating Petition - Queens County, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Caltabiano Election Materials, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Christ the King Hall of Fame, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Community Events, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Election Press, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Federazione Political Contributions, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Friends of Maltese Campaign Debt Letter, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - GRYC Newsletter - Maltese Community Center, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - I Love Animals, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Italian American Organizations, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Resolution: Triangle Shirtwaist Factory, 2009 (Oversize 1, Folder 33)
  - Letters for Seminerio, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - New York State Conservative Party, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Spargo Character Reference, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Stuyvesant High School, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Veterans Day Press - Queens Chronicle, 2009 (Oversize 1, Folder 34)
  - Messano Campaign, 2009; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - All Faiths Cemetery, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Aqueduct, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Associazione Culturale Italiana di New York, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Board of Elections Executive Director, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Carrigan, Ray - Death Notices, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Certificate from Korean President, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Clippings, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Community Events, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Fricke, Carla, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Italian American Organizations, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Kudlow Draft, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Legislation Introduced by Senator Maltese, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter on Behalf of Salvatore Cottone, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Maltese, Constance, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - New York State Conservative Party, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - New York State Election Returns, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - New York State Republican Committee Poll, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Political Events, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Paladino Campaign, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Queens Republican Party, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Recommendation Letters, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Schwartz, Barry, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Stop, Question, and Frisk Policing Practices in New York City, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Stuyvesant High School Alumni Association, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Tax Cut Party Petition, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Triangle Fire Association NYU Memorial, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Veterans, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Board of Elections Clips and Memos, 2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Triangle Fire Survivor History, 2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - ACU and CPAC, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - King, Peter, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Haggerty, John Jr. - Clippings, 2010-2011; Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Adams, Marge - Obituary, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Clippings, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Community Events, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Italian American Organizations, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - LaGuardia Community College Maltese Education Center, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Queens Clippings, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Queens Republican Party, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Ridgewood Times 9/11 Retrospective, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Second Chance Program, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Seminero, Tony, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Slagus, Raymond - Death Notice, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Stuyvesant High School Reunion, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Triangle Fire Memorial Association, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - ACU Board Members, 2011; Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - All Faiths Cemetery, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Christ the King, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Clippings, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Community Events, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Conservative Party of Richmond County, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Election Materials, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Italian American Museum, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Newsletters, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Poll Watcher's Guide, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Queens News Clippings, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire Memorial, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - American Conservative Union, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Bilski Recommendation Letter, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Catsimatidis Campaign, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Clippings, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Community Events, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Complaint: U.S. vs. Smith et al., 2013 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Ferraro, Geraldine Campus Dedication, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Italian American Organizations, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Korean War Anniversary Event, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Korean War Memorial, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Korean War Museum, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Lhota, Joe Campaign, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - National Review - Getting Out the Vote, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Newsletters, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Queens County Bar Association Golden Jubilarian, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Reyes, Catherine & Juan Campaign, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Trunzo, Caesar Memorial, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Biographies, 2013; Undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Clippings, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Community Events, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Queens County Republican Committee, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Ragusa, Phil Obituary, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Scharfenberger Appointment, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Senate Club Photos, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Stuyvesant High School Alumni Association, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Clippings, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Culley Induction Invitation, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Hartman, Richard Obituaries, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Richmond Hill Community Center Fundraiser, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Tabone, Vincent, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence, 2015; Undated (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Bruno Book Party Invitation, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Clippings, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Italian American Organizations, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Queens Veterans Day Parade, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - United Veterans War Council, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Stuyvesant High School Alumni Association, 2016; Undated (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Christ the King 40th Anniversary, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Clippings, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Columbus Association, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Italian American Organizations, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Malliotakis, Nicole - Campaign, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Queens Veterans Day Parade, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Stuyvesant High School Alumni Spectator, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Columbus Press Clippings, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Maltese, Constance - Memorial, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Manhattan College Reunion, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Christ the King Plaque Dedication, 2019 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Clippings, 2019 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Lifetime Achievement Award, 2019 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - NYSCP - Salute to Michael Connors, 2019 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Clippings, 2020 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Quinn, Jim Campaign, 2020 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Shulman, Claire Obituary, 2020 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Triangle Fire Memorial Association, 2021 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Federalist Society Status Report, Undated (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Photos from John Jay College Gallery - Constance Portraits, Undated (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Notes and Ephemera, Undated (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire History, Undated (Box 1, Folder 140)